downloadbestsoft.com 2018-12-25

# Fosshub | Privacy

### Dear visitor, please read our Privacy Policy

We encourage all visitors ( users ) to read our PRIVACY POLICY and also our TERMS OF USE ( also known as Terms of Agreement ). By simply accessing this website you agree and you accept all of our terms and conditions and also our privacy policy that can be changed any time without any notification since we do not keep, store or manage any email address databases.   
If you can read this privacy policy available for www.FossHub.com, it means that you agree with all the terms listed here. If you do not agree with our privacy policy you should leave this website immediately without visiting any other website page.   
To help you make decisions about the information you provide anywhere on this site, this notice has been provided to outline our practices.   
You should know that we respect your privacy, and we will never sell your information to anyone.   
Also, we hate spam as much as you do, so you will only ever get an email from us that you have asked for and we have personally approved.   
We use secure hosting accounts and other security measures to protect our database and any information provided.   
Any e-mail you receive from this site will be sent as an answer to a question of yours made via the contact form or an old contact. We do not keep an email database.

### Tracking

We don’t directly track your presence on this website. Your IP address is logged and we look at the server logs on occasion, but this is in an aggregate fashion for the purpose of determining why people come to visit us.   
Example   
The websites that link to us and send traffic here, and what keywords people use to find us via search engines such as Google, Yahoo, and MSN.   
We do not build or associate such data to create a user profile or to track you.   
Also, we do not share or sell such data. To make sure that we stay transparent, we remove the logs that are stored automatically at a certain period of time. We do not store such logs for a long period. 

### Cookies (Third-Party Cookies that do not belong to FOSSHUB)

Please note that FOSSHUB opted to show only "Non-personalized ads" to European visitors. You can read more about Google EU User Consent Policy here.   
“Cookies” are data sent to your web browser from a web server (such as Google) that can uniquely identify your computer and store information about user preferences. Most web browsers will accept cookies by default, but they can be set to reject cookies, either from all websites or from specific sites. You can also manually delete cookies from your web browser. These options are generally set through a “Privacy” setting in your browser setup.   
You can choose to remove them through your browser settings.   
Please click on the following links to adjust your browser settings: 

Some of these set web browser cookies. Google in particular quietly collects a tremendous amount of data on your browsing habits, and we participate in that data collection.

### General information to all international visitors ( updated 16 August 2012 )

We would like to inform you that we are now using Google interest-based advertising technology. This technology is implemented by "us" www.FossHub.com using Google. This will not be used to identify you or your location, it will be used only to help our advertising system ( AdSense ) provided by Google to show more relevant Ads to our visitors.   
We also use the DoubleClick DART cookie from Google. What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?   
"The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web."   
"Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet."   
"We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. "   
Besides Google AdSense we also use Google Analytics which may collect data. We can't say what kind of data is being collected, for more information you might want to check/read for their privacy policy or terms of agreement - please see the links below: 

Visit this page frequently to check with our Privacy Policy   
Proofreading kindly provided by Marisano James
